朽木字幕组
如有错误请联系：
QQ: 474249394
翻译：
飞越无限
校对：
压制：
飞越无限
Ox. Box. Fox.[Sofia在学习]
Ox. Box. Fox.
-Bullock先生 －早上好
-Mr Bullock. -Good morning.
早上好 Sofia 很抱歉 打扰你学习了
Morning, Sofia. Sorry to interrupt your lesson.
－我们结束了 －很抱歉 索菲亚  我们还没结束
-We're finished.-No, we're not, Sofia...
我们下楼继续学习
and we'll continue downstairs.
矿山被分给了三个郡
Hills get divided into three counties.
每个郡都有一个特派员
Each county has a commissioner.
－由谁来认命？ －州长
-Appointed by fucking who? -The governor.
－什么时候任命？ －已经任命了
-When the fuck does that happen? -lt already did.
－有我认识的人么 －是从杨克顿直接下派的
-Anyone I know? -They're all from Yankton.
Well 作为信使 尽管带来的是个坏消息
Well, being as you're the bearer of unsettling news...
为什么你他妈的不进来呢？
why don't you step the fuck inside?
没有矿区的人，huh？
No one from the fucking hills, huh?
都是Pennington的人
All Pennington's people.
省点功夫吧
Saves time.
用不用找个地方 杀了他们
Just travel to one destination,murder the three of them...
看他们死了怎么当物派员
see how they like being commissioner after they're dead.
马车到了 Lila
Coach coming, Lila.
－你的朋友和姑娘们 也一起来了？ －我不清楚
-With your friend and her girls? -I don't know.
马车还在上路上
It's still way up in the hills.
－你想让我和你一起去看看？ －Oh 不 不
-You want me to come watch with you? -Oh, no, no.
Well 好吧
Well, okay.
Well 你忙你的 我在外面等你
Well, do whatever you want, but I'll wait outside for you.
所有这些收据 除了Hendy lron的这张
All the invoices other than this mission from Hendy lron
都付清了
have been acted on.
我明白了
I see.
你签个字 然后我先付清一部分
You'll note I've made partial payment to them.
好的
Yes.
看看是不是有重复的
Questioning a possible duplication.
－防止捣鬼？ －恩
-For the billhooks? -Yes.
－这个是我的资产总额？－那个是存款总额
-ls that my worth? -That's the amount on deposit.
你的财产相当的多
Your worth is considerably more.
多谢您的用心打理 Bullock先生
Thank you for your attention in all these matters, Mr Bullock.
不客气
You're welcome.
他给你写了封信　Pennington
He wrote you a letter. Pennington.
－你到现在才给我？－我总得先交待一下我知道的吧
-That you held from me till now?　-To say what I knew first.
坐下吧
Please be seated.
没错 我现在得用这玩意才能读东西了
Yes, it has fallen to this.
Damn
Damn.
Ellsworth先生
Mr Ellsworth.
Garret夫人的黄金准备运往丹佛了么？
Is the Garret gold in readiness for shipment to Denver?
没错
That it is.
在主人为你们送行之前我感觉会耽搁一下
I'd expect a delay before the owner blesses its passage.
而小Sofia和她的家庭教师又不在场
While little Sofia is off with her tutor...
Garret夫人会和Bullock磋商一下
Mrs Garret consults with Mr Bullock.
好吧
All right.
以Bullock的能力 当然 作为她的法定代理人
In Bullock's capacity, of course, as her claims trustee.
大家心知肚明 我不想再听你说什么了
That's all the cleverness on that subject I'm inclined to hear from you.
Fat. Cat.
饼干？刚出炉的
Biscuits? Piping fresh.
Yeah 我们都还年轻
Yeah, when both of us was young.
无论如何 我得方便一下
Anyways, I could use a bath.
‘我必须告知您 Swearengen先生
l urge you, Mr Swearengen,
我并非想损害您的利益‘
not to take as injury to your interest...
‘我只是任命了杨克顿方面的特派员’
"my appointing only men from Yankton.
对于不是这此区域的特派员 …’
"For, not being of the region, such men serving as commissioners...
‘我不会妨碍你们 比如你
"l hold less likely to obstruct those like yourself...
以及那些在矿山里讨生活的人’
"who actively pursue their destinies in the hills.
‘恕我冒昧 我对您的支持致以殷切的希望
"ln those brave endeavours, be assured of my best hopes...
高度的尊重 和无尽的感激
"high esteem, and continued gratitude for your gestures of support.
州长 Pennington‘
"Governor Pennington."
Well 就说了这些？
Well, that's just the fucking sort.
把他们剁碎 撇一边去
Chop them into pieces and each of them happily slithers away...
省得当你面放屁
still lying to your fucking face.
Well 我现在要怎么应付这封信？
Well, what am I to make of this, now?
你还不知道他的目的
You don't know yet what he wants to do.
我已经知道怎么处理我送的财物了
Knew what to do with them fucking bribes I sent
那是他们应得的礼物
That's a gift they're born with.
你想拿回来也很难
Far as how hard to move on the camp...
而且他也没保证他会反对
he ain't sure yet all he'd be going against.
也许这能当做杀他们的理由
Maybe that is cause for cutting some throat.
那就中了他的圈套了
That'd put you right where he wants you.
如果你换个他没料到的方法解决了问题，…
If you got other ways to move on him is what he ain't clear about.
信息源于无形
Messages from invisible sources...
也可以认为是科技的进步
or what some people think of as progress
历史记载的不是野蛮人用的烽火狼烟么？
Ain't the heathens use smoke signals all through recorded history?
这是什么操蛋逻辑
How's that a fucking recommendation?
well 在我看来信件从一个人寄到另一个人
Well, it seems to me like letters posted one person to another...
只是比烽火这种东西慢了一点
is just a slower version of the same idea.
你上次接到陌生人的来信是他妈的什么时候的事了？
When's the last time you got a fucking letter from a stranger?
－我爸爸去世 －去世？
-Bad news about Pa. -Bad news.
损害我们的利益的企图就是我们和陌生人的唯一的沟通方式
Tries against our interests is our sole communications from strangers...
所以无论如何 我们得到处立电线杆
so by all means, let's plant poles all across the country...
好让我们赶紧用电线传递美言来奉承那个混蛋
festoon the cocksucker with wires to hurry the sorry word...
然后他都不屑于我的想法 huh？
and blinker our judgements of motive, huh?
你比我想的还多
You've given it more thought than me.
事情现在还不够糟么？
Ain't the state of things cloudy enough?
难道我们面对的不是无法预计的么？
Don't we face enough fucking imponderables?
well 以上帝的名义 你说句话 我就把这些电线杆烧了
Well, by God, you give the word, Al, and them poles will be kindling.
我们已经做完了 你不高兴么？
After we've made love, are you sometimes happy?
我从床上起来了 你感到很奇怪么？
Because I get up from the bed, is that why you wonder?
我要合计一些事
I'll intend something...
我起来 坐下之后才发现我想得都是你
come to myself realising I've only stood or sat...thinking about you.
比如现在 想的是你的脚趾很漂亮
Just now, that your toes are beautiful...
也在打算重燃激情
when I'd intended to replenish the kindling.
我相信这是真的
I was raised believing...
玩忽职守是获得快乐的一种可行的方法
dereliction of duty is the one sure way to happiness.
[Bullock本职是她的代理人及财产看护人]
小酌怡情 但要节制
So often with you I've been perfectly happy.
我可以开始装货
Can I start the shipment loading...
好让那些人不喝酒么？
keep the men from falling to drink?
好的 开始吧
Yes, please.
我相信你[他要押运的是黄金]
Now I believe in you.
开始装货
Start loading.
如果我想得到那些货 Bullock认为
Does Bullock think if I wanted...
那四个拿枪的骑兵会阻止我么？
them four horsemen with rifles would ward me off that woman's gold?
可能是防备其他人的吧
Maybe it's just precautions against other operators.
没有措施能保护的了她
No precautions of his protect her.
其他人 即便是他们的祖宗 也要尊重我
Them other operators forebear out of respect for me...
他们知道你的刀上鲜血的意味
and knowing what hot blood your blade would draw...
如果他们敢想的话
if they ever fucking presumed.
他并不是想羞辱你
He don't intend it as insult.
我说的是Bullock 这只是我的想法
Bullock, that's my point.
不幸的是 你言中了
Horror is, you're fucking right.
他都不知道他是怎么出气的
He don't know if it's breathing or taking it in through fucking gills.
他也就会造爱
He is that fucking cunt-struck.
他们就是童话中的空中气泡 比空气还轻
They're a float in some fairy fucking bubble. Lighter than air.
他 她抢过去的 还有他的那个该死的徽章
Him, her snatch, and his stupid fucking badge.
－哪传来的？－我猜是10号矿区
-Where's that from? -My guess would be Number 10.
希望不是Tom Nuttall出事了
Hope it ain't Tom Nuttall taking the quick fucking way out.
不 不是 他在那儿
No. No, there's himself.
我就是在自欺欺人 当我认为美国已经接纳我们的时候
Self-deceiving cocksucker I am, I thought when America took us in...
Bullock就会证明这是个该死的想法
Bullock would prove a fucking resource.
看看他 像个粗俗癫狂的主教一样走路
Look at him, striding out like some randy maniac bishop
治安官 这是你的份内之事啊 huh？
Sheriff! About his duties to the camp, huh?
幸运的是麻烦事没再出现的早点 huh Bullock？
Luck trouble didn't jump out earlier, huh, Bullock?
差点被发现你的小弟弟的兼职
Might have found you mid-thrust at other business.
那又是什么呢？ 让我们开开眼？
What is it? Taken by a vision?
你不会喜欢像你正在盯着我这样被人盯着地
You would not want to be staring like that at me.
只是Bummer Dan 我想他被杀了
It's only Bummer Dan, but I think he's killed.
－离我远点 －我哪也不去
-Be where I can find you. -I ain't going no place.
－我去拿把长枪 －不用
-I'll go get my big gun. -No.
那不是解决问题的办法
That ain't how this wants to resolve.
你下楼照看下生意吧
You go down, Dan, see to the cunt and whiskey.
你想要我留在这么？ －你去洗你的澡吧
-You want me up here? -You, go take your bath.
你想让驴集中注意力
You want a donkey's attention...
你就得用个杆子放在他的两耳中间撑着
bring a fucking pole down between his ears.
Jeez. Ow. Fuck.[尿结石疼了]
Jeez. Ow. Fuck.
我绝没想过伤害这个人 或者不利于他
No ways did I wish that man harm or take against him.
你射杀了他 huh?
You did shoot him, huh?
只是这个夹克的缘故
Only on account of the jacket.
我从其他的酒鬼那听说过他
I'll hear it from the other drunks.
Harry把Bummer Dan错认为Slippery Dan了
Harry mistook Bummer Dan for Slippery Dan.
之前Slippery Dan掏出鸡巴 在痰盂里撒尿
That had pulled his cock out previous, started filling the cuspidor yon.
will 长话短说
Will, keep this short.
Well Harry大声喝斥Slippery他停下来
Well, Harry shouts for Slippery to stop...
但Slippery把他的鸡巴转向了Harry
but Slippery cast his johnson toward Harry...
越过吧台向他撒尿
pisses at him over the bar.
我抽出了枪 治安官
I pulled my gun, Sheriff.
我警告Slippery‘滚出去 你被驱逐了
I told Slippery, "Get out, you're ruled off for the day...
从你弄湿那扇门开始到明天破晓之前
"you darken that door before dawn tomorrow...
否则我开枪打死你
"I'll shoot you fucking dead."
Harry的衣服的前襟上还有尿印呢
Harry's shirtfront's urine-sopped still.
但这是Bummer Dan
But this is Bummer Dan.
Oh 上帝 这是真的
Oh, my God, it's true.
Well 这就是Slippery
Well, that's Slippery.
Bummer死了
Bummer's fucking dead.
他们都知道了 你这个肮脏的喷尿的畜生
They know that, you filthy piss-spraying beast!
起来吧
Get up off your knees.
－Oh 上帝啊 -站起来 告诉我关于这事你所知道的
-Oh, my God. -Get up and tell your part in this.
治安官 我知道的就是Bummer穿得是我的夹克
My part, Sheriff, was putting Bummer in my jacket...
然后把可怜的自己扔在了这儿
and sending the poor fuck in here.
为什么？
To what purpose?
我想如果Harry乍一看到Bummer
Thinking maybe if Harry winged one at Bummer...
可能会把他错认成我，他曾威胁要杀了我
mistaking him for me, threatened to murder...
这会很有意思
it'd be funny.
那我有什么责任 Bullock先生？Hey 是不是对挑衅反应过激？
What's my liability, Mr Bullock? Hey, ain't getting pissed on provocation?
你没杀成你打算杀的人 或者说你打算杀掉你想杀的那个人
You didn't kill who you meant to or mean to kill the man you did.
那我的责任呢？ 更严重么？
What's my liability? Worse in some way?
收殓他 把他好好葬了
Box him and see he's buried.
但我告诉你们俩 都给我安生点
But I'm telling both of you, watch it!
我可以拿回我的夹克么，副官？
May I retrieve my jacket off of him, Deputy?
yeah 拿吧
Yeah, go ahead.
上帝 这是我开过的最操蛋的玩笑
Gee, worst fucking joke I ever played!
真不知道我干嘛要喝那么多
Don't know why I drinks the way I do.
他要是再掏出鸡巴来 就开枪
Pulls that prick stunt again, shoot him.
－等一下 Bullock－我有私事 多谢
-Wait up, Bullock. -Private business, thanks.
如果Swearengen得到了左膀右臂 这就不是私事了
It won't be private if Swearengen's got his cappers at his flanks.
真得是有私事 抱歉 Charlie
It's private. Thank you, Charlie.
带中奖的肥皂
Soap with a prize inside.
你的肉里能中奖么 上尉？
You got any prizes in that meat there, Captain?
这个混蛋
This cocksucker.
朋友 我的肥皂里有奖品
Friend, I got soap with a prize inside.
你已经被警告过在守法的生意人和你
You were told to keep an interval...
之间保持点距离
between yourself and legitimate merchants.
我已经保持距离 治安官 这是他们主动找得我
I keep my interval, Sheriff. It's their increase what's crowding me.
我们要数25步 现在是第14步 和我一起数
We're gonna count out 25 paces. We're at 1 4. Count them with me.
－15 －15
-Fifteen. -Fifteen.
-16, 1 7, 18...-16, 1 7, 18...
-19, 20. -19, 20.
怎么了 Joanie Stubbs和Lila小姐
Why, Joanie Stubbs and Miss Lila.
是什么在这个春光明媚的早上把你们吸引出来了？
What brings you to the air this fine spring morning?
俾斯麦演的戏剧[意指Swearengen]
Stage from Bismarck.
俾斯麦 你是说？
Bismarck, you say?
我们不都在盼望着新的到达者么？
Don't the kid in all of us look forward to the new arrival?
震耳发聩啊
I still tingle at the bottom of my balls.
那会是谁呢？海耶斯总统？
Who could it be? President Hayes?
也可能是变戏法的 或者画像的
Maybe it's jugglers or face painters.
你感觉到了么 甜心
Where do you feel it, honey?
感觉到了
The bottom of your balls.
气氛有点沉闷啊
Air's gone a little fixed.
我认为你知道是谁造成地
I guess we know who fixed it.
不好意思[因为有男的而有所顾忌]
Excuse me.
妈妈 看那个小溪里的人
Look at the man in the creek, Mama.
他在为自己的将来生活而工作
He's panning for his fortune.
但是 bullock是不会做这种工作的
Won't see Mr Bullock in the creek, though.
－是的 －你说的是那个治安官么？
-No. -Didn't you say he was the Sheriff?
Bullock and Star五金店的合伙人 朽木镇的治安官
Part owner of Bullock and Star Hardware, Sheriff of Deadwood Camp.
混蛋
Cocksuckers!
Bullock.有事么？
Bullock.
你是要让我回去么？
Do I need to watch my back against you?
AI说都别掺和他的事
Al said to stay out of it.
早上好啊
Morning.
如果你珍惜你的同伙性命的话 Star先生
If you'd spare your partner a gutting, Mr Star...
那么你就应该现在就去GEM酒吧了[宝石沙龙酒吧]
you might make your way to the Gem.
谁要杀他[gutting 去内脏]
A gutting at whose hand?
他在街道上的时候 我老板大声地叫他了
My boss called him out clear across the thoroughfare.
无缘无故地就想杀他？
Unprovoked?
他正在照看着Garret夫人的利益 你的搭挡
He was seeing after Mrs Garret's interests, your partner...
当我老板喊他的时候
when my boss shouted.
－替我锁门 －好的
-Lock up for me, please. -Sure.
你老板应该跟我学学想开点
Your boss should do like me and learn to look the other way!
那就不是他了
It ain't his line.
岁月不饶人啊 否则我一点都不惧你
Age impedes my stream, no fucking fear of you.
进来吧
Get in here.
都是身不由己
All in due fucking course.
但是你得先告诉我 Bullock 我怯战了么？
But tell me one thing first, Bullock, as I stand here fucking humbled.
寡妇Gattet
Does the widow Garret...
试图找个有经验的矿工和5个捣矿机
have a going fucking hard-rock concern and five-stamp mill...
来日夜不停的从石英里开始采金了么？
crushing gold out of her quartz all day and fucking night?
什么？
What?
但她贡献给营地一些钱财 好让其他人也
But does she cast her lot with the camp… furnish others here
有机会发财了么？
a chance to develop what they got to hang on or even prosper?
你个圆脸混蛋
You pie-faced cocksucker.
过来 为你的无礼负责
Get in here and account for your insult.
或者 你应该提醒她一下 在有其他的部位接触时
Or, with you at her ear, among other points of entry...
履行一下你的义务  她是把货都送到的Denver吧
instead of doing your civic duty, does she ship her fucking loot to Denver?
公民义务？
Civic duty?
她被娘家和夫家反对
Opposed by her own and her dead husband's family...
把财产置于这个没有法律 政府也名副其实的营地里
to put her assets at play in camp with no law or government worth the name?
看看她现在 时来运转了 公民义务？
See as here where she lives and struck lucky, civic duty? Yeah.
现在是时候让她或者其他人
And it's time for her and some others...
不要再逃避了责任了 杨克顿方面开始动作了
to quit their fucking shirking. Yankton's making its move.
－真操蛋－什么意思
-The fucking thing! -Meaning what?
‘杨克顿方面有所动作’ 恕我冒昧
"Yankton's making its move?" Without more insults.
我们要被干了 拆成郡
We're getting ass-fucked. Carved into counties...
特派员还不是我们的人
with not one fucking commissioner coming from the hills.
你怎么知道的？
How do you have this information?
从一份花费良多的州长的亲笔信里
From the governor himself in a pricey little personal note.
他们想把我们变成杨克顿的长期饭票
They want to make us a trough for Yankton's snouts.
他们贪婪的大脑袋已经伸到外面了
And them hoopleheads out there...
他们需要支持 好彻底解决这些混蛋
they need buttressing against going over to those cocksuckers.
现在 我能处理我的地方
Now, I can handle my areas...
但还有些地方是我管不了的
but there's dimensions and fucking angles I'm not expert at.
但你能 如果你强势地足够久的话
You would be if you'd sheathe your prick long enough.
－闭嘴 －并且重拾
-Shut up. -And resume...
去年下天的那个让我们震撼的行事风格
being the upright pain in the balls that graced us all last summer.
闭嘴 你个混蛋
Shut up, you son of a bitch.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
Bullock.
婊子有的是
The world abounds in cunt of every kind...
她也是其中之一
including hers.
好吧
Of course...
如果能让你不做傻事
if it would steer you from something stupid...
我可以换个姿态
I could always profess another position.
你会藏刀在身么？
Will I find you've got a knife?
我不需要刀
I won't need no fucking knife.
他们从阳台掉下来了
They went over the fucking balcony!
不幸的是
Awful possibility in these matters...
两个人都会很疼
is both men sustaining mortal injury.
你找死 混蛋
You looking to die, cocksucker?
－你不能杀他 －该死的
-He ain't your kill! -God damn you!
Hey hey hey 别再往前走了
Hey, hey. Hey, don't come no further!
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
万能的上帝啊
Jesus Christ almighty!
－Bullock在哪呢 －我擦
-Where's Bullock? -Fuck me.
我有刀
I do have a knife.
现在刀在我手上
It come to me now.
欢迎来到朽木镇
Welcome to fucking Deadwood!
这儿很好战的
It can be combative.
我还真是少有的幸运啊
But I'm rarely that fucking lucky.
扔个便士在犹太人鼻子上吧(指的是邮局老头查理斯)
Wave a penny under the Jew's nose.
他还活着(子弹擦着耳边飞过)
They got living breath in them...
老天眷顾他(应该叫做幸运便士？)
it brings them right around.
Bullock先生
Mr Bullock.
－真是惊喜－没人死亡
-A happy surprise. -No one's dead.
Star先生的肩受伤了
Mr Star's shoulder's been hurt.
那不是你们的高档妓女朋友Maddie么？
Ain't that your high-end whore friend Maddie?
是的
Yes.
我记得她不是把家当搬到了纽约么？
That I thought had took her snatch to New York?
是的
Yes.
太好了 人们开始闲逛了
Wonderful how folks can get around now.
医生Cochran需要从Whitewood镇赶回来么？
Doc Cochran needs to come from Whitewood.
Yeah
Yeah.
A.W. Merrick.
Star和Utter先生先扶到我们的店里吧
Mr Star and Utter should be taken to our store.
好的
All right.
你好 Bullock先生
Hello, Mr Bullock.
你好  William
Hello, William.
我很好
I’m all right
我会很感激你们
I'd be grateful...
如果帮忙把她们的行李搬到屋子里
if you'd take their belongings to a house...
我在西边建的那所
I built on the west edge.
让我来给Maddie看座吧 Joanie.
Better let me hold Maddie's chair, Joanie.
我得给人家一个好的印象
I need to make a fucking impression.
－女士 －大人
-My lady. -My lord.
我对我的疏忽很抱歉
Lack of notice is my only regret.
是我的错 没先告诉Joanie
That's my fault for giving Joanie none.
你做好最坏打算了么 Maddie
Were you hedging your bets, Maddie?
来这个营地我早已无所畏惧了
Feared losing my nerve all the way to the camp.
我想知道的是 马车不是把你带到了葛底士堡么 huh?
Then wondered, had that coach brought you to Gettysburg, huh?
葛底士堡 战场
Gettysburg, fucking battle carnage.
－是的 我听着呢 －什么？
-Yes, I wondered. -What?
津津有味
Wondered.
你买下了那所房子 甜心 什么时候的事？
You secured that building, honey, when?
11月
November.
11月拿到了那所房子？
Got the building in November...
我以为你会在那之后找到
I guess you'll be operating out of?
我本以为这就是个闹剧 过后就忘了 因为Joanie的钱
I'd have thought a trick would have been behind it, but Joanie's fuck money...
已经花在了珠宝上
has been going for jewels.
我们互相了解已经多长时间了 甜心？
How long we had that understanding, honey?
从我14岁开始
Since I was 14.
我给她珠宝
I've been giving Joanie jewels...
作为她的嫖资 从她14岁开始
for her fuck money since she was 14 years of age...
不止一次我站出来保护她
and not once did I come out ahead.
无论如何
Anyways.
Anyways....
从11月开始
Since November...
我感觉这事要不了了之了 但我猜
it looked to me the project lay fallow, but I guess...
它那时刚刚开始吧
it was just germinating.
-我们能私下谈谈么 Cy？-那会显得失礼么？
-Shall we talk in private, Cy? -Would that be rude?
一点也不
Not at all.
我是说 我和Joanie18年的交情了
I mean, a 18-year relationship between me and Joanie...
所以你能离开一下么
and just one moment alone?
当然可以
Of course not.
如果你愿意 也可以顺便做点生意
Suck some pricks if you like.
嫖资你都留着把 就当是我给你的礼物了
Keep whatever they give you as my way of saying welcome.
这会有不开眼的看上我么？
Any blind ones out there?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
-绷带得缠紧点 AI -缠吧
-That bandage wants to be tight, Al. -That does it!
你把它缠自己脖子上试试 [太他妈紧了]
Ask it if it wants to be wound around your fucking neck!
离我远点 Barney
Get away from me, Barney!
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
欠干的Adams
Fucking Adams.
他制止了你  不是么？
Restrained you, didn't he?
在大道上他阻止了我 现在他又想找个小妞了
Obstructs me in the thoroughfare. Now he wants to bill and coo.
擦
Fuck!
那个犹太人是怎么想的呢 Dan 想拿手枪扑过来？
What was that Jewish fellow thinking, Dan, to charge at me with a purse gun?
这事我也不常见
This is an unfamiliar situation.
他只是有点过于想证明自己了
He just overplayed trying to prove himself.
总之整件事是因什么而起呢？
What was that whole damn thing about anyhow?
AI想把Bullock拉过来
Al's calling Bullock to the fold.
Bullock也不是AI一路的啊
Bullock ain't even of Al's flock.
AI现在想招点人 但不当做心腹
Al's gonna be calling numbers to the fold now that he can't trust like us.
即便是他不喜欢的人
Some he don't even like.
我们要并入美国了
We're joining America.
满嘴谎言 你不能信那帮混蛋
And it's full of lying, thieving cocksuckers that you can't trust at all.
州长 特派员 以及其他类似的
Governors, commissioners, whatnot.
以上帝的名义 那有点难以接受
By God, that's just the new way of things.
你只要习惯就行了 Jonhnny
And you just gonna have to get used to it, Johnny.
-好吧 -你不能不接受
-All right. -You gonna have to accept it...
并学会控制住自己
and learn to control yourself.
你不必和我争论了
You get no argument from me!
好吧
Okay.
是我逼你的 小姐
It's been me nudging you from the nest, young lady...
-逼你飞走的 -好吧
-urging you to take fucking wing. -Okay.
你从哪得来的钱买那个地方
Where did the money come from that bought that place?
你爸爸以6.5美元的价格把你卖给了我
Your daddy sold me you for $6.50...
而有个有钱的亲戚也很难瞒住我的
so a rich relation is tough to swallow.
别对我撒谎就是对我的尊重 honey
It is respectful not to lie, honey...
但是要是继续沉默就别怪我不客气
but any further silence will get me violent.
你知道钱是哪来的
You know where that backing came from.
Eddie Sawyer的临别赠礼？
A farewell gesture from Eddie Sawyer!
我知道Eddie从我这偷钱[Eddie负责赌博]
I knew Eddie had been stealing from me...
后来他跑了 同时你突然买了那个地方
and then he flees and you turn up owning that place.
我不会再在这工作了 Cy 你明白么？
I don't work here no more, Cy. You understand?
无论发生什么？
No matter what.
杀了你或者放你走
It's kill you or let you go.
我能忍心让你死么？
Could I make it with you dead?
为什么要试呢？
Why try?
看看
Look at that.
看看这动人的微笑
Look at that beautiful smile.
好吧 亲爱的
All right, darling.
让我
Let me...
让你走吧
Iet you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们要不要
Shall we....
我要出去一下 当Maddie
I'll take the air while Maddie...
听到这个好消息的时候
hears the happy news.
让我们去找那个老太婆
Let's go get the fucking crone.
我感觉自己是个孩子 我想蹦起来
I feel like a boy. I feel like skipping.
我祝福你 鼓励你
I'm that fucking hopeful and excited for you.
热水
Hot water.
告诉吴
Tell Wu...
最好别用酒鬼喂猪
that that drunk better not get ate by his pigs...
直到我找到办法处理尸体
until I have had my way with the corpse.
我做好准备了 医生 如果你想开始挖子弹的话
I'm braced, Doc, if you want to start digging.
马上
Momentarily.
谢谢 夫人 耳鸣
Thank you, ma'am. The ringing....
我很好 William
I'm all right, William.
你的枪和徽章哪儿去了 Bullock先生？
Where are your gun and badge, Mr Bullock?
我和那个和我打架的人是私人恩怨
It was personal between me and the man I fought...
所以我摘下了
so I took them off.
但他有刀啊
But he kept a knife.
我卸掉武器的时候并不知道
I didn't know that when I disarmed.
那你现在要因为那把刀逮捕他么？
Will you arrest him now for the knife?
你问的够多了 William
That's questions enough for Mr Bullock, William.
给他点鸦片酒
Give him a little dose of that laudanum.
我受得了 医生
I got my load on, Doc.
毋庸置疑
Don't doubt...
我会拿回我的枪和徽章
I'll have back my gun and badge.
擦
Fuck.
我留意到了这些东西在你的夜壶里 知道这不是你的
I found these seeing to your piss-pot, and I know they ain't yours.
什么告诉你的 那个该死的徽章？
What tipped you off, the fucking badge?
放下
Put them down.
值得背后高兴么
Is that some kind of private fucking hilarity?
-什么？-观察我的夜壶
-What? -The piss-pot remark.
不
No.
早上我把尿
I made water...
从阳台泼出去了如果这是你该干的事的话
off the balcony this morning, if it's any of your fucking business.
现在离我远点
Now get away from me.
不是你 EB 回来
Not you, E.B. Get the fuck back here.
老天啊
Heavens.
就像发生了史诗般的战斗
It's all like some great Greek battle.
Yeah 医生呢 Huh？
Yeah, how about that fucking Doc, huh?
去诊治道貌岸然的人
Seeing to the respectable types...
却扔下我们 这些定期的主顾 huh？
Ieaving us, the ones that pay him regular, huh?
那么 那个女的和孩子
So, that woman and child...
是Bullock的？
Bullock's?
他的妻子和儿子
His wife and son.
Star先生 Charlie Utter都怎么样了
How was Mr Star? How was Charlie Utter?
闭嘴 Johnny
Shut up, Johnny!
查清Bullock被打成什么样了
Detail Bullock's condition.
衣服坏了 视线模糊
The worse for wear. No clarity to his look or focus...
当我查看其他参与者的时候
as I could cite in other combatants.
你碰我了 EB
You touch me, E.B...
我他妈要把你鼻子穿过你脑袋
I'll put your nose through your fucking brain!
NOW 他说他下一步的打算了么
Now, did he state his further intentions?
拿回枪和徽章
To have his gun and badge back.
用什么语气
In what fucking tone?
Well
Well...
直呼你的名字让我受宠若惊 AI 他当时在对一个8岁孩子讲话
I'd shy from putting a name on it, Al. He was talking to an 8-year-old.
听上去就像他会回来要求更多一样？
Sound like he'd be coming back for more?
Well 我不想猜 以免猜错
Well, I'd hate to guess and be wrong.
马车上有新的妓女 huh？
New whores on that coach, huh?
查清他们在哪工作
Find out where they'll be working.
我可以把东西带给他 顺便探探他的底
I could take him his gun and badge, plumb his intent as we talk.
那你们的谈话要怎么开始呢 huh？
And how would that chat start, E.B., huh?
‘这是你的东西 而他看起来就像个逼一样’
"Here's your hardware, and as he looks a cunt anyway...
‘无论如何AI想让你接受胜利者的荣誉’
"Al would like you to have this rose."
我去调查一下新的妓女
I'll look into the new whores.
你要怎么处理
How you doing?
子弹取出来了么？Star先生还活着？
Is my bullet out? Will Star live?
－如果他死了 他会高兴一些 －Utter先生呢？
-lf he don't, he's going happy. -And Mr Utter?
－他会瞎了或者聋了么？－不会的
-Will he be blind and deaf? -No!
我得弄点新的情报 在我又被责难之前
Let me suss out that new trim, Johnny, before I earn some added rebuke.
看 正如我说的那样 我不是你们的敌人
Look, all's I'm saying is, I ain't your enemy.
无论你怎么想 如果我认为你做得事十次有九次是有敌意的
Whatever you thought your intentions was coming on me like you did...
那第十次就会是你这辈子的最后一次行动
nine times out of ten, that'll be the last fucking move you ever make.
Bullock会回来拿武器
Bullock will be coming back for his weapon.
－出于什么目的？－涵待解决的问题
-To what intent? -Open question.
Well 我们会做好准备的
Well, we'll be ready.
你开始你的第一次了
You've had your one out of 10.
孩子瞪着眼睛向马车外看 我就那么娘么？
Cow-eyed kid looking from that coach, that's what fucking unmanned me.
他应该不知道她要来的
He couldn't have known she was coming.
就在今天 我询问Bullock他家庭的情况
Just today, I'd asked Mr Bullock after his family and...
他没提她们已经在路上了
he made no mention of their being en route.
Well 您真好 还搭把手
Well, you're kind, extending the hand of welcome.
Well 最好这个营地能禁止外来者
Well, at its best, this camp can be forbidding to new arrivals.
那就有点过了
That was very much my experience.
更不用说一来就看到Bullock先生在道上的泥里打滚
Let alone to come upon Mr Bullock in the mud of that thoroughfare...
还受伤了 谁知道会有多严重呢
injured, who knows how seriously?
Well谢天谢地 他是自己走回去的
Well, thank goodness, he seemed coming back to himself.
lsringhausen小姐 我没意识到医学
Miss lsringhausen, I didn't realise medicine...
也是你的擅长领域
was among your areas of expertise.
这不是 Garret夫人
It isn't, Mrs Garret.
也许我该了解一下Bullock先生的现在情况
Then perhaps, I'll better learn Mr Bullock's condition in his presence.
－以及Star'先生和Utter先生的情形 －是的 夫人
-And Mr Star's and Utter's condition. -Yes, ma'am.
Sofia?
你把彩带绑在了糖果上？
You put a ribbon around your candy?
你想让我把这个送给那个男孩？
And did you want me to give it to that boy?
－请出声回答 Sofia－是的
-Please answer in words, Sofia. -Yes, please.
－lsringhausen小姐－Ellsworth先生
-Miss lsringhausen. -Mr Ellsworth.
我来Garret夫人当保镖
I'm here to steer Mrs Garret.
那么Ellsworth和我要一起去送东西
Then Mr Ellsworth and l will make the delivery.
问个我不该问的 Garret夫人
Not as I'd been asked, Mrs Garret...
但我感觉换一天拜访也许更好
but I wonder if this ain't a call better paid another day.
我不敢相信我能再找个合适的机会拜访
I've stopped believing I can dictate the terms of my opportunities.
Well 有人说 不抓住机会
Well, some would say, it might be your choice...
也算是一种选择
what chances you decide not to take...
有些人就是堵不住他的嘴
some being the butt-in loudmouth types.
－我可以一个人走么－不 夫人
-Shall I walk on alone, Mr Ellsworth? -No, ma'am.
不好意思我吐出来了
I'm sorry for throwing up.
如果你没有 我就有点怀疑你的以前的习惯了
If you hadn't, I'd suspect your previous habits.
－Bullock先生－Garret夫人
-Mr Bullock. -Mrs Garret.
－你觉得怎么样 Star先生－我吐了两次
-How are you feeling, Mr Star? -I've puked twice.
－Garret.夫人－Trixie
-Mrs Garret. -Trixie.
Garret夫人
Mrs Garret.
－Utter先生－夫人
-Mr Utter? -Ma'am.
不必惊慌 都是旧伤
Don't be alarmed. A lot of this damage is old.
我可以介绍一下我的妻子Martha和我们的儿子William么？
May I introduce my wife Martha and our son William?
Alma Garret夫人
Mrs Alma Garret.
-你好 -你好
-How do you do? -How do you do?
-你好 William -你好
-How do you do, William? -How do you do?
这是Ellsworth Garret夫人事务的执行总裁
And Ellsworth, who superintends Mrs Garret's claim
-夫人 William -你好
-Madam. William. -How do you do?
你可能发现我们现在处境不妙
You've discovered us in distressing circumstances
我们很安全 而且也很高兴联系上了Bullock先生
We're safe and glad of joining Mr Bullock.
我希望这些对你们能有点用处
I hope this can be of some use to you...
-对你们安家 -谢谢
-in your settling in. -Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的孩子给你儿子的礼物也在里面
My ward includes sweets for your son...
如果他妈妈允许他接受的话
when his mother decides he may have them.
-你孩子是个男孩？ -是个女孩 叫Sofia
-ls your ward a boy? -A girl, Sofia.
-比你小点 我感觉 -Oh
-A little younger than you, I think. -Oh.
谢谢
Thank you.
你想起我信里提过Garret夫人吧
You recall Mrs Garret from my letters.
是的
Yes.
你能拿到信真是好运
That's good luck you had right there.
因为我是送信的。但我得今天得承认我一直很外行
Because I carry the mail, and I'll admit today before laypeople...
弄丢的比我送到的要多
we lose more letters than we deliver.
那我就走了啊！希望很快能再次见到你
I'll say good-bye then, in hopes that I see you again soon.
好吧
Yes.
-希望也能见到你 William -谢谢你的好意
-I hope I see you soon, William. -Thanks for the sweets.
可以来找我问那些好的钓鱼地点哦
And don't be pestering me for the good fishing spots.
我在中央旅馆吃早饭时候才给它们起得名字
I name them only over breakfast at the Grand Central Hotel...
或者是我叫狗的时候
or, when I call my dog.
-你想看下你房子么？-我很想
-Will you see your house? -I would like to very much.
Bullock夫人 我从你之前的东西里取回了你的帽子
Mrs Bullock, I've retrieved your bonnet from your former post...
在你方便的时候
and at your convenience...
黑山先锋报的读者很想听听
the readers of the Black Hills Pioneer would be interested in...
您的旅途趣闻 可能的话还有您的对营地的第一印象
hearing about your journey and perhaps, your first impressions of our camp.
你不必全都回答他们
You don't have to give them all.
-谢谢你 请照看Star先生-好的。不用急着回来
-Thank you for seeing to Mr Star. -No need to hurry back.
走吧！William
Go ahead, William.
你写给他老婆的信里都没提我 是不？
He never wrote of me in his letters to her, did he?
Garret夫人 我们也没谈他在信里写了什么或者没写什么啊
We never spoke on what he's wrote to his wife or hadn't, Mrs Garret.
或者 他为什么没写
Or why he hadn't.
不知道
No, ma'am.
我们俩也不应该谈这个
And you and me hadn't ought to, either.
谢谢你陪我过来 Ellsworth先生
Thank you for taking me, Mr Ellsworth.
不客气 夫人
You're welcome, ma'am.
你想起
You'll recall...
我信里关于他丈夫的事了么？
what I wrote about her husband?
他怎么要回买矿山的钱的
How he'd sought his money back on a claim?
摔死了
He died in a fall...
在获赔之前 却发现那是个富矿
before gaining satisfaction, and the claim proved out rich.
是那所房子么？ 前面那所很漂亮的
Is that the house, sir, the splendid one ahead?
是的
It is.
你可以先走一步 William
You can walk ahead a little piece, William.
但不能走远
Just a little piece.
出于承诺 我得帮这个寡妇一把
And, of my promise to help the widow...
尽我所能
as I could...
-我答应野牛Bill Hickok的 -我明白 Bullock先生
-made to Wild Bill Hickok. -Yes, Mr Bullock.
白天的工作肯定已经让你筋疲力尽了
And you must be as weary from the day's events...
我们赶来时你又在准备屋子
and your work readying the house as we are from travel.
别再劳烦自己了
Please don't trouble to repeat yourself.
我们和那个女的以及她儿子一路来的
We travelled with that woman and her boy.
当她和你们一起在路上时
While the lady was travelling with you...
他丈夫人 那个治安官 正把阴茎插在另一个女人身体里
her husband, the Sheriff, was pickling his prick in the cunt brine of another.
看看Lila 这些未经人事 鲜嫩的雏鸟们
Look at Lila, delivering her ducklings all undamaged and dry.
-我们要怎么庆祝 CY? -我会投给坚强而精练的人
-How are we gonna celebrate, Cy? -My vote's for hardy but brief.
这是不会计票的
Votes don't count here just yet.
酒有点少 Lila
It looks a little small, Lila.
但我猜你们能够充分利用地
but I guess you gals are used to making the best of that.
就是过程有点快 让我为一个新的试水者干杯
Just fleeting as fucking innocence, let me toast a bold new venture.
-你的场子叫什么名字 甜心？－Le Chez Ami(朋友之家)
-Your place got a name yet, honey? -Le Chez Ami.
好记
That's catchy.
张嘴 伸舌头
Open your yap, stick out your tongue.
敬朋友之家
To the Chez Ami!
也敬…伸出舌头
And to.... Stick your fucking tongue out!
Joanie和Maddie
Joanie and Maddie!
妓院行业的能手
Able hands at a whorehouse tiller!
也敬
And to...
Doris
Doris.
贝拉联盟最好的混蛋之一
One of the Bella's best cocksuckers...
我把她送你以示友好
that I send with them as a gesture of friendship.
我们有姑娘了
We have the girls we need.
一路平安 小可爱 旅途就像我们刚才讲的法语这样长
Bon voyage, sweetheart, as long as we're speaking French.
我们的人真的够了 Cy
We got all the girls we need, Cy.
别担心她是个钉子 Joanie 请不要在这点上和我争了
Don't fear that she'll spy, Joanie. Please don't reject Doris on that basis.
你得到的是我忍痛给你的 我是认真的
You'll just get her belly cut by me showing you I'm serious...
一个没开苞的贝拉妓女送给你们了
and an uncut Bella whore sent with you.
朋友之家是用从我这偷的钱建立的
Being as funds stole from me by Eddie, put the Chez Ami on its feet...
我认为我就是投资者
I consider myself an investor and I will...
我要拿到我的那份 6成
have my interests looked at, 60 cents from dollar one.
就需要人监管
But a true count fucking verified!
好吧
All right.
Lila 带这群姑娘离开 Doris 你最好开始收拾下行李
Get these girls out of here, Lila! You better get packed, Doris!
你会带上我给你买的东西么？
Did you bring anything with you when I bought you?
那好了 甜心 你就带上你随身擦东西的抹布得了
That's all right, honey. You just pack the rags you been wiping the cum off with.
-好吧 Joanie -是的 我们要走了
-All right, Joanie? -Yes, and now we're gonna go.
你怎么看 认为我像动物园里的猴子么？
What do you think, I'm a monkey in a zoo?
Think I'm gonna throw my shit
after you?
不是
No.
不要像跟个猴子讲话那样对我
Don't fucking talk to me like I'm a monkey.
带着这群妓女离开这
Get those cunts out of here!
到你看到她死
Don't believe there's no good women...
我也不信有好女人了
till you've seen one with maggots in her eyes.
Joanie!
走之前赌一把 你正鸿运当头
Bet the wheel before you leave. You're on a lucky run.
-小溪里有鱼么？- 有时会有
-ls there fish in this stream? -Sometimes.
这就是了
This is it.
-我们可以进屋了么？-你收到关于这所房子的信了么？
-May we go inside? -Did you get the letter about the house?
我收到了
I did get that letter.
-信在我箱子最上面 －我就是想知道一下
-It's at the very top of my trunk. -That has all my thoughts.
我们能进屋么？
May we go in?
我应该现在回去 你和孩子先进去吧
I should go back now. You and the boy go in.
我们进屋吧 Bullock先生给我们造的 William
Let's go in the house Mr Bullock has made us, William.
－来吧 Bullock先生 －现在不行 William
-Come on, Mr Bullock. -Not just now, William.
你不想进来么？
Don't you want to come in?
我现在还不能进去
I can't come in just now.
在你巡视过营地 拿回枪和徽章之后么？
After you've seen to the camp, gotten your gun and badge back?
我会陪妈妈进去
I'll take mother in.
多谢
Thank you.
来吧
Come on.
多谢
Thank you.
‘亲爱的Bullock夫人 你的房子快完工了’
"Dear Mrs Bullock, your house is near finished.
我没有放任木材商和工人干活而不管
"My satisfaction does not exceed the camp"s lumbermen and sawyers...
我不厌其烦地审视木材成色
""whose patience I have tried by my over-watchful eye for greenness...
以及木板锯得是否齐整
""and for good square-edge quality in the cut boards.
我选择了一年生的松木
""I"ve chosen pine...
来建造地基 桩 梁和椽
""one-year seasoned, for the sills, posts, floor joists, and rafters.
其它的框架材料是云杉
""The other framing timber is of spruce.
承压的地方
""Where partitions bear upon them...
我加了两层来撑住地板
""I have doubled the beams and supported the floor...
桩打入地面三尺
""with locus posts set three feet into the ground.
我认为你看到竖框窗户会笑出声来
""I think you may laugh to see the mullioned windows...
从客厅就能看到整个营地
""with their view of the camp from out the parlour.
还有完工 他们就目炫神迷了
""Being unfinished, they look like unfocused eyes.
我留下所有最终装饰的工作给你
""I"ve left these and all final decorative choices...
鉴于你高雅的品味
""to your superior judgement and sensibility. ""
肥皂 能中奖的肥皂
Soap! Soap with a prize inside!
我希望你们能安然抵达
""I hope that you and the boy may arrive in good health and safety.
我期待我们能更深入的了解彼此
""I look forward to our opportunity to better get to know each other.
我祈祷作为我哥哥的接替者
""I pray that in my brother"s stead...
对于孩子王我能成为称职的父亲
""I may be permitted to be a father to the boy...
和Robert 做得一样好
""as good as Robert would have been...
作为丈夫 能照顾你 让你幸福安康
""and as to your care and comfort and safety, as good a husband to you.
谨启 Seth Bullock
"Yours sincerely, Seth Bullock. ""